A Guide to the Commonwealth Fund records, Living at Home Program, SG 1, Series 24 FA296
Rockefeller Archive Center
Commonwealth Fund records, Living at Home Program, SG 1, Series 24
1985-1989
Rockefeller Archive Center
Commonwealth Fund
FA296
10.64 Cubic Feet 28 letter document boxes
Conditions Governing Access note
Open for research with select materials restricted as noted. Brittle or damaged items are available at the discretion of RAC.
Biographical/Historical note
The Commonwealth Fund was established in 1918 with an endowment of $10 million from Mrs. Stephen V. Harkness for "benevolent, religious, educational and like purposes." The early grants supported a variety of programs while generally promoting welfare, especially child welfare. Several grants were made in the field of medical research, but the Board of Directors decided in 1920 that this field was already sufficiently supported by other philanthropic organizations.
Despite this decision, by the mid-1920s the chief interest of the Fund had become public health, including mental hygiene, community health, rural hospitals, medical research, and medical education. Other grant areas included war relief, educational and legal research, child welfare, and international medical fellowships.
File Plan note
Former Classification: IX; IV 4B 4
Other Finding Aids
Other available finding aids describing the Commonwealth Fund records include:
FA247 Commonwealth Fund Harkness House drawings
FA276 Commonwealth Fund records, Annual Reports, SG 1, Series 4
FA277 Commonwealth Fund records, Archives/Library, SG 1, Series 5
FA278 Commonwealth Fund records, Austrian Program, SG 1, Series 6
FA279 Commonwealth Fund records, Board of Directors, SG 1, Series 7
FA280 Commonwealth Fund records, Capital Grants, SG 1, Series 8
FA281 Commonwealth Fund records, Child Health Demonstrations, SG 1, Series 9
FA282 Commonwealth Fund records, Division of Community Clinics, SG 1, Series 10
FA283 Commonwealth Fund records, Division of Health Studies, SG 1, Series 11
FA284 Commonwealth Fund records, Division of Public Health, SG 1, Series 12
FA285 Commonwealth Fund records, Division of Publications, SG 1, Series 13
FA286 Commonwealth Fund records, Division of Rural Hospitals, SG 1, Series 14
FA287 Commonwealth Fund records, Educational Research, SG 1, Series 15
FA288 Commonwealth Fund records, English Mental Hygiene Program, SG 1, Series 16
FA289 Commonwealth Fund records, Finance Committee, SG 1, Series 17
FA290 Commonwealth Fund records, Grants, SG 1, Series 18
FA291 Commonwealth Fund records, Harkness Family, SG 1, Series 19
FA292 Commonwealth Fund records, Harkness Fellowships, SG 1, Series 20
FA428 Commonwealth Fund records, Harkness Fellowships, Fellows Reports, SG 1, Series 20A
FA293 Commonwealth Fund records, Institute for Child Guidance, SG 1, Series 21
FA294 Commonwealth Fund records, Interface Program, SG 1, Series 22
FA295 Commonwealth Fund records, Legal Research Program, SG 1, Series 23
FA296 Commonwealth Fund records, Living at Home Program, SG 1, Series 24
FA297 Commonwealth Fund records, Mental Hygiene Program, SG 1, Series 25
FA298 Commonwealth Fund records, Miscellaneous - unprocessed
FA299 Commonwealth Fund records, Personnel - unprocessed
FA300 Commonwealth Fund records, Pilgrim Trust, SG 1, Series 28
FA301 Commonwealth Fund records, Program for the Prevention of Delinquency, SG 1, Series 29
FA302 Commonwealth Fund records, Reference Files, SG 1, Series 30
FA303 Commonwealth Fund records, Reports of the General Director, SG 1, Series 31
FA304 Commonwealth Fund records, Treasurer, SG 1, Series 32
FA305 Commonwealth Fund records, Turndown Lists, SG 1, Series 33 - unprocessed
FA306 Commonwealth Fund records, Vertical File (R. Fitz), SG 1, Series 34 - unprocessed
FA307 Commonwealth Fund records, Visual Materials, SG 1, Series 35
FA389 Commonwealth Fund records, Administration - Historical Files, SG 1, Series 1
FA390 Commonwealth Fund records, Administration - Officers Files, SG 1, Series 2
FA429 Commonwealth Fund records, President, Margaret E. Mahoney, SG 2, Series 1
FA430 Commonwealth Fund records, Book Program, SG 2, Series 2
Scope and Contents
Types of records include: grant files and applications.
Medical research; Medical education; Legal research; Legal issues; Mental health; Medicine -- Scholarships, fellowships, etc.; Medicine, Rural; Education, Rural; Child welfare; Law; Hygiene; New York (N.Y.); New York (State); Child psychology; Child mental health; United States; War relief; Public health; Public welfare
- Program History, undated (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Program History, undated (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Program History, undated (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Program Overview and Summary of Projects, undated (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Blank Copy of Application, undated (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Grant Recipients - Areawide Aging Agency - General, September 1986-July 1989 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Grant Recipients - Areawide Aging Agency - Application and Abstract, January-April 1986 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Grant Recipients - Areawide Aging Agency - Assessment Instruments, January 12, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Grant Recipients - Areawide Aging Agency - Award Letter, Grant Agreement, Budget, Financial Reports, Tax Documents, May 1986-February 1989 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Grant Recipients - Areawide Aging Agency - Evaluation, February 12, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 10)
- Grant Recipients - Areawide Aging Agency - Progress Reports, February 1987-June 1988 (Box 2, Folder 11)
- Grant Recipients - Areawide Aging Agency - Progress Reports, December 1988-June 1989 (Box 2, Folder 12)
- Grant Recipients - Areawide Aging Agency - Site Visit Reports, March-June 1988 (Box 2, Folder 13)
- Grant Recipients - Areawide Aging Agency - Work Plan, September-October 1986 (Box 2, Folder 14)
- Grant Recipients - Community Care Organization - General, September 1986-May 1989 (Box 2, Folder 15)
- Grant Recipients - Community Care Organization - Applicaiton and Abstract, April 17, 1986 (Box 2, Folder 16)
- Grant Recipients - Community Care Organization - Assessment Instrumetns, undated (Box 2, Folder 17)
- Grant Recipients - Community Care Organization - Award Letter, Grant Agreement, Tax Documents, April-November 1986 (Box 2, Folder 18)
- Grant Recipients - Community Care Organization - Budget, Financial Reports, December 1986-December 1988 (Box 2, Folder 19)
- Grant Recipients - Community Care Organization - Progress Reports, October 1987-April 1989 (Box 2, Folder 20)
- Grant Recipients - Community Care Organization - Site Visit Report, January-February 1988 (Box 2, Folder 21)
- Grant Recipients - Community Care Organization - Work Plan, October 1986-September 1987 (Box 2, Folder 22)
- Grant Recipients - Coordinated Care Management Corporation - General, April 1986-May 1989 (Box 3, Folder 23)
- Grant Recipients - Coordinated Care Management Corporation - General, April-September, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 24)
- Grant Recipients - Coordinated Care Management Corporation - Application and Abstract, January 1986-March 1987 (Box 3, Folder 25)
- Grant Recipients - Coordinated Care Management Corporation - Assessment Instruments, 1986-1988 (Box 3, Folder 26)
- Grant Recipients - Coordinated Care Management Corporation - Award Letter, Grant Agreement, Financial Reports, Tax Documents, April 1986-January 1989 (Box 3, Folder 27)
- Grant Recipients - Coordinated Care Management Corporation - Progress Reports, July 1987-June 1989 (Box 3, Folder 28)
- Grant Recipients - Coordinated Care Management Corporation - Work Plan, 1986-1987 (Box 3, Folder 29)
- Grant Recipients - Council for Jewish Elderly - General, September 1986-May 1989 (Box 3, Folder 30)
- Grant Recipients - Council for Jewish Elderly - Application and Abstract, undated (Box 4, Folder 31)
- Grant Recipients - Council for Jewish Elderly - Award Letter, Grant Agreement, Tax Documents, November 1986-June 1987 (Box 4, Folder 32)
- Grant Recipients - Council for Jewish Elderly - Budget, Grant Agreement, Financial Reports, January 1987-June 1989 (Box 4, Folder 33)
- Grant Recipients - Council for Jewish Elderly - Evaluation, July 22, 1987 (Box 4, Folder 34)
- Grant Recipients - Council for Jewish Elderly - Progress Reports, October 1986-June 1987 (Box 4, Folder 35)
- Grant Recipients - Council for Jewish Elderly - Progress Reports, September-November 1987 (Box 4, Folder 36)
- Grant Recipients - Council for Jewish Elderly - Progress Reports, December 1987-October 1988 (Box 4, Folder 37)
- Grant Recipients - Council for Jewish Elderly - Site Visit Report, September 17; 19??* (Box 4, Folder 38)
- Grant Recipients - Council for Jewish Elderly - Work Plan, August 13, 1986 (Box 4, Folder 39)
- Grant Recipients - Council of Community Services - General, September 1986-October 1988 (Box 4, Folder 40)
- Grant Recipients - Council of Community Services - Application and Abstract, April 22, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 41)
- Grant Recipients - Council of Community Services - Assessment Instruments, undated (Box 5, Folder 42)
- Grant Recipients - Council of Community Services - Award Letter, Budget, Grant Agreement, Financial Reports, June 1986-September 1988 (Box 5, Folder 43)
- Grant Recipients - Council of Community Services - Progress Reports, February-August 1987 (Box 5, Folder 44)
- Grant Recipients - Council of Community Services - Progress Reports, October 1987-August 1988 (Box 5, Folder 45)
- Grant Recipients - Council of Community Services - Progress Reports, May 1988-June 1989 (Box 5, Folder 46)
- Grant Recipients - Council of Community Services - Site Visit Report, September 18-23, 1987 (Box 5, Folder 47)
- Grant Recipients - Council of Community Services - Work Plan, August 28, 1986 (Box 6, Folder 48)
- Grant Recipients - Council on Aging - General, September 1986-May 1989 (Box 6, Folder 49)
- Grant Recipients - Council on Aging - Application and Abstract, undated (Box 6, Folder 50)
- Grant Recipients - Council on Aging - Award Letter, Budget, Grant Agreement, Financial Reports, Tax Documents, May 1986-February 1987 (Box 6, Folder 51)
- Grant Recipients - Council on Aging - Evaluation, December 1987-March 1988 (Box 6, Folder 52)
- Grant Recipients - Council on Aging - Progress Reports, September 1986-February 1989 (Box 6, Folder 53)
- Grant Recipients - Council on Aging - Site Visit Report, September 1987-May 1989 (Box 6, Folder 54)
- Grant Recipients - Council on Aging - Work Plan, undated (Box 6, Folder 55)
- Grant Recipients - Duke University Medical Center - General, September 1986-November 1988 (Box 6, Folder 56)
- Grant Recipients - Duke University Medical Center - General, December 1988-May 1989 (Box 6, Folder 57)
- Grant Recipients - Duke University Medical Center - Application and Abstract, undated (Box 6, Folder 58)
- Grant Recipients - Duke University Medical Center - Assessment Instruments, undated (Box 6, Folder 59)
- Grant Recipients - Duke University Medical Center - Award Letter, Budget, Grant Agreement, Tax Documents, February-May 1986 (Box 6, Folder 60)
- Grant Recipients - Duke University Medical Center - Evaluation, December 9, 1987 (Box 6, Folder 61)
- Grant Recipients - Duke University Medical Center - Progress Reports, June 1986-March 1989 (Box 6, Folder 62)
- Grant Recipients - Duke University Medical Center - Site Visit Report, April-July 1987 (Box 7, Folder 63)
- Grant Recipients - Duke University Medical Center - Work Plan, undated (Box 7, Folder 64)
- Grant Recipients - East Harlem Council for Human Services - General, September 1986-May 1989 (Box 7, Folder 65)
- Grant Recipients - East Harlem Council for Human Services - Application and Abstract, January-April 1986 (Box 7, Folder 66)
- Grant Recipients - East Harlem Council for Human Services - Award Letter, Budget, Grant Agreement, Financial Reports, Tax Documents, April 1986-January 1989 (Box 7, Folder 67)
- Grant Recipients - East Harlem Council for Human Services - Progress Reports, April 1987-August 1988 (Box 7, Folder 68)
- Grant Recipients - East Harlem Council for Human Services - Progress Reports, July 1988-July 1989 (Box 7, Folder 69)
- Grant Recipients - East Harlem Council for Human Services - Site Visit Report, November 1986-April 1987 (Box 7, Folder 70)
- Grant Recipients - East Harlem Council for Human Services - Work Plan, 1987-1989 (Box 7, Folder 71)
- Grant Recipients - Huntington Memorial Hospital - General, September 1986-May 1989 (Box 8, Folder 72)
- Grant Recipients - Huntington Memorial Hospital - Application and Abstract, undated (Box 8, Folder 73)
- Grant Recipients - Huntington Memorial Hospital - Assessment Instruments, undated (Box 8, Folder 74)
- Grant Recipients - Huntington Memorial Hospital - Award Letter, Budget, Grant Agreement, Financial Reports, Tax Documents, April 1986-August 1988 (Box 8, Folder 75)
- Grant Recipients - Huntington Memorial Hospital - Progress Reports, February-October 1986 (Box 8, Folder 76)
- Grant Recipients - Huntington Memorial Hospital - Progress Reports, October 1986-February 1987 (Box 8, Folder 77)
- Grant Recipients - Huntington Memorial Hospital - Progress Reports, January-May 1987 (Box 8, Folder 78)
- Grant Recipients - Huntington Memorial Hospital - Progress Reports, August 1987-May 1989 (Box 9, Folder 79)
- Grant Recipients - Huntington Memorial Hospital - Site Visit Report, February 11, 1987 (Box 9, Folder 80)
- Grant Recipients - Huntington Memorial Hospital - Work Plan, October 1986-September 1987 (Box 9, Folder 81)
- Grant Recipients - Medical Care and Research Foundation - General, September 1986-July 1989 (Box 9, Folder 82)
- Grant Recipients - Medical Care and Research Foundation - Application and Abstract, undated (Box 9, Folder 83)
- Grant Recipients - Medical Care and Research Foundation - Assessment Instruments, December 1986-January 1987 (Box 9, Folder 84)
- Grant Recipients - Medical Care and Research Foundation - Award Letter, Budget, Grant Agreement, Financial Reports, Tax Documents, May 1986-August 1988 (Box 9, Folder 85)
- Grant Recipients - Medical Care and Research Foundation - Progress Reports, April-September 1987 (Box 9, Folder 86)
- Grant Recipients - Medical Care and Research Foundation - Progress Reports, March-September 1988 (Box 10, Folder 87)
- Grant Recipients - Medical Care and Research Foundation - Site Visit Report, February-December 1987 (Box 10, Folder 88)
- Grant Recipients - Medical Care and Research Foundation - Work Plan, 1986-1989 (Box 10, Folder 89)
- Grant Recipients - Miami Jewish Home and Hospital - General, September 1986-May 1989 (Box 10, Folder 90)
- Grant Recipients - Miami Jewish Home and Hospital - Application and Abstract, 1986 (Box 10, Folder 91)
- Grant Recipients - Miami Jewish Home and Hospital - Award Letter, Budget, Grant Agreement, Financial Reports, Tax Documents, April 1986-February 1989 (Box 10, Folder 92)
- Grant Recipients - Miami Jewish Home and Hospital - Evaluation, July 1987-February 1988 (Box 10, Folder 93)
- Grant Recipients - Miami Jewish Home and Hospital - Progress Reports, January 1987-September 1989 (Box 10, Folder 94)
- Grant Recipients - Miami Jewish Home and Hospital - STEMS - Case Management Manual, undated (Box 10, Folder 95)
- Grant Recipients - Miami Jewish Home and Hospital - Work Plan, November 12, 1986 (Box 10, Folder 96)
- Grant Recipients - Montefiore Hospital Association - General, September 1986-May 1989 (Box 10, Folder 97)
- Grant Recipients - Montefiore Hospital Association - Application and Abstract, April 18, 1986 (Box 10, Folder 98)
- Grant Recipients - Montefiore Hospital Association - Assessment Instruments, undated (Box 11, Folder 99)
- Grant Recipients - Montefiore Hospital Association - Award Letter, Budget, Grant Agreement, Financial Financial Reports, Tax Documents, April 1986-January 1989 (Box 11, Folder 100)
- Grant Recipients - Montefiore Hospital Association - Progress Reports, June 1987-January 1988 (Box 11, Folder 101)
- Grant Recipients - Montefiore Hospital Association - Progress Reports, June 1988-June 1989 (Box 11, Folder 102)
- Grant Recipients - Montefiore Hospital Association - Site Visit Report, October -November 1987 (Box 11, Folder 103)
- Grant Recipients - Montefiore Hospital Association - Work Plan, 1986-1989 (Box 11, Folder 104)
- Grant Recipients - New York Hospital - General, August 1987-May 1989 (Box 11, Folder 105)
- Grant Recipients - New York Hospital - Application Abstract, undated (Box 11, Folder 106)
- Grant Recipients - New York Hospital - Assessment Instruments, undated (Box 11, Folder 107)
- Grant Recipients - New York Hospital - Award Letter, Budget, Grant Agreement, Financial Reports, Tax Documents, April 1986-January 1989 (Box 11, Folder 108)
- Grant Recipients - New York Hospital - Progress Reports, June 1987-March 1989 (Box 12, Folder 109)
- Grant Recipients - New York Hospital - Site Visit Report, 1988 (Box 12, Folder 110)
- Grant Recipients - New York Hospital - Work Plan, September-October 1986 (Box 12, Folder 111)
- Grant Recipients - New York Hospital - Contract Letters - General, 1988 (Box 12, Folder 112)
- Grant Recipients - New York Hospital - Contract Letters - Assessment and Enrollment, 1987 (Box 12, Folder 113)
- Grant Recipients - New York Hospital - Contract Letters - Ongoing Case Management, 1987-1988 (Box 12, Folder 114)
- Grant Recipients - New York Hospital - Contract Letters - Short-Term Care, 1987 (Box 12, Folder 115)
- Grant Recipients - Northern California Presbyterian Homes - General, September 1986-May 1989 (Box 12, Folder 116)
- Grant Recipients - Northern California Presbyterian Homes - Application and Abstract, undated (Box 12, Folder 117)
- Grant Recipients - Northern California Presbyterian Homes - Assessment Instruments, undated (Box 12, Folder 118)
- Grant Recipients - Northern California Presbyterian Homes - Award Letter, Budget, Grant Agreement, Tax Documents, April-November 1986 (Box 12, Folder 119)
- Grant Recipients - Northern California Presbyterian Homes - Progress Reports, October 1986-February 1987 (Box 13, Folder 120)
- Grant Recipients - Northern California Presbyterian Homes - Progress Reports, December 1987-September 1988 (Box 13, Folder 121)
- Grant Recipients - Northern California Presbyterian Homes - Progress Reports, February-September 1989 (Box 13, Folder 122)
- Grant Recipients - Northern California Presbyterian Homes - Site Visit Report, March 1988-June 1989 (Box 13, Folder 123)
- Grant Recipients - Northern California Presbyterian Homes - Work Plan, August 19, 1986 (Box 13, Folder 124)
- Grant Recipients - Pima Council on Aging - General, September 1986-May 1989 (Box 13, Folder 125)
- Grant Recipients - Pima Council on Aging - Application and Abstract, undated (Box 13, Folder 126)
- Grant Recipients - Pima Council on Aging - Assessment Instruments, undated (Box 13, Folder 127)
- Grant Recipients - Pima Council on Aging - Award Letter, Budget, Grant Agreement, Tax Documents, April 1986-November 1987 (Box 14, Folder 128)
- Grant Recipients - Pima Council on Aging - Progress Reports, August 1986-December 1988 (Box 14, Folder 129)
- Grant Recipients - Pima Council on Aging - Site Visit Report, February 1987-February 1988 (Box 14, Folder 130)
- Grant Recipients - Presbyterian Hospital - General, May 1986-May 1989 (Box 14, Folder 131)
- Grant Recipients - Presbyterian Hospital - Application and Abstract, April 22, 1986 (Box 14, Folder 132)
- Grant Recipients - Presbyterian Hospital - Assessment Instruments, December 26, 1986 (Box 14, Folder 133)
- Grant Recipients - Presbyterian Hospital - Award Letter, Budget, October 1986-August 1987 (Box 14, Folder 134)
- Grant Recipients - Presbyterian Hospital - Evaluation, November 24, 1987 (Box 14, Folder 135)
- Grant Recipients - Presbyterian Hospital - Progress Reports, January 1987-September 1989 (Box 14, Folder 136)
- Grant Recipients - Presbyterian Hospital - Site Visit Report, May 1986-July 1987 (Box 14, Folder 137)
- Grant Recipients - Presbyterian Hospital - Work Plan, 1986-1987 (Box 14, Folder 138)
- Grant Recipients - Ramsey County Public Health Nursing Service - General, September 1986-May 1989 (Box 14, Folder 139)
- Grant Recipients - Ramsey County Public Health Nursing Service - Application and Abstract, January 31, 1986 (Box 14, Folder 140)
- Grant Recipients - Ramsey County Public Health Nursing Service - Assessment Instruments, 1987 (Box 15, Folder 141)
- Grant Recipients - Ramsey County Public Health Nursing Service - Award Letter, Budget, Grant Agreement, Financial Reports, Tax Documents, April 1986-September 1988 (Box 15, Folder 142)
- Grant Recipients - Ramsey County Public Health Nursing Service - Progress Reports, October 13, 1987 (Box 15, Folder 143)
- Grant Recipients - Ramsey County Public Health Nursing Service - Progress Reports, February 1988-July 1989 (Box 15, Folder 144)
- Grant Recipients - Ramsey County Public Health Nursing Service - Site Visit Report, September-October 1988 (Box 15, Folder 145)
- Grant Recipients - Ramsey County Public Health Nursing Service - Work Plan, September 22-29, 1986 (Box 15, Folder 146)
- Grant Recipients - South Cove Community Health Center - General, July 1986-May 1989 (Box 15, Folder 147)
- Grant Recipients - South Cove Community Health Center - Application Abstract, January-April 1986 (Box 15, Folder 148)
- Grant Recipients - South Cove Community Health Center - Assessment Instruments, undated (Box 15, Folder 149)
- Grant Recipients - South Cove Community Health Center - Award Letter, Budget, Grant Agreement, Financial Reports, Tax Documents, May 1986-August 1988 (Box 15, Folder 150)
- Grant Recipients - South Cove Community Health Center - Progress Reports, October 1986-June 1989 (Box 15, Folder 151)
- Grant Recipients - South Cove Community Health Center - Site Visit Report, February-October 1988 (Box 15, Folder 152)
- Grant Recipients - South Cove Community Health Center - Work Plan, undated (Box 15, Folder 153)
- Grant Recipients - St. Vincent's Hospital - General, September 1986-May 1989 (Box 16, Folder 154)
- Grant Recipients - St. Vincent's Hospital - Application and Abstract, undated (Box 16, Folder 155)
- Grant Recipients - St. Vincent's Hospital - Award Letter, Budget, Grant Agreement, Financial Reports, Tax Documents, October 1986-May 1988 (Box 16, Folder 156)
- Grant Recipients - St. Vincent's Hospital - Evaluation, January 15, 1988 (Box 16, Folder 157)
- Grant Recipients - St. Vincent's Hospital - Progress Reports, July 1987-September 1989 (Box 16, Folder 158)
- Grant Recipients - St. Vincent's Hospital - Site Visit Report, December 1988-February 1989 (Box 16, Folder 159)
- Grant Recipients - St. Vincent's Hospital - Work Plan, September 24, 1986 (Box 16, Folder 160)
- Grant Recipients - University Hospital, Home Medical Service - General, September 1986-May 1989 (Box 16, Folder 161)
- Grant Recipients - University Hospital, Home Medical Service - Application and Abstract, undated (Box 17, Folder 162)
- Grant Recipients - University Hospital, Home Medical Service - Assessment Instruments, 1987 (Box 17, Folder 163)
- Grant Recipients - University Hospital, Home Medical Service - Award Letter, Budget, Grant Agreement, Financial Reports, Tax Documents, April 1986-January 1987 (Box 17, Folder 164)
- Grant Recipients - University Hospital, Home Medical Service - Award Letter, Budget, Grant Agreement, Financial Reports, Tax Documents, February 1987-January 1989 (Box 17, Folder 165)
- Grant Recipients - University Hospital, Home Medical Service - Evaluation, September-November 1987 (Box 17, Folder 166)
- Grant Recipients - University Hospital, Home Medical Service - Progress Reports, August 1986-December 1987 (Box 17, Folder 167)
- Grant Recipients - University Hospital, Home Medical Service - Progress Reports, June 1988-June 1989 (Box 17, Folder 168)
- Grant Recipients - University Hospital, Home Medical Service - Site Visit Report, December 1987-October 1988 (Box 17, Folder 169)
- Grant Recipients - University Hospital, Home Medical Service - Work Plan, February 27, 1987 (Box 17, Folder 170)